Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - September 1986
    - Divestment Protest at A.D. White Statue, 860919 (Box 18)
    - Slide Copies (Broken Pipe/ M. Kelly/ Violinist), 860920 (Box 18)
    - Ken Wilson with ravi Sudan in Experimental Area - Olin Hall, 860921 (Box 18)
    - New Faculty - WSH Memorial Room, 860922 (Box 18)
    - C.O.L.E. Copiers and RPU Interiors and Exteriors, 860923 (Box 18)
    - Beebe Lake Construction, 860924 (Box 18)
    - PRAVDA/ Ken Wilson, 860925 (Box 18)
    - Willard Straight Engineering Faculty/ RPU Faculty Fellows, 860927 (Box 18)
    - Gargoyles/ Geri Gay with Computer, 860928 (Box 18)
    - Hotel School Kickoff Construction, 860929 (Box 18)
    - Randy Shew's Retirement Party (Color), 860930 (Box 18)
  - October 1986
    - News service, 861001 (Box 18)
    - Development, 861002 (Box 18)
    - Baker Institute- girl with dog, 861003 (Box 18)
    - Panel Discussion - Science and the Law, 861004A (Box 18)
    - Olant Schence / Plant Science, 861004B (Box 18)
    - Michael Kammen/Music Faculty/Sibley Ext., 861005 (Box 18)
    - Campus Map, 861006 (Box 18)
    - Law School Forum, 861007 (Box 18)
    - Dian Fossey Items, 861008 (Box 18)
    - New Faculty (Voelcker, Owens, Farnum, Parks, DeVault, Trumbull, Simon, Seeley, Freeman, Wiggins, Blake, Thomas, David & Sue Williams, Ko, Beneria, Dear, Anantharum) / Campus Scenes / Engr. Check Passing, 861009
      - Contact sheet (Box 18)
    - Francine Herman, 861010 (Box 18)
    - David Taylor-Way wtth video camera & screen, 861011 (Box 18)
    - RPU graphic designer, Hungry Bear, 861012 (Box 18)
    - Theory Center Inaugural Celebration, 861013 (Box 18)
    - RPU nursery school, 861014 (Box 18)
    - Jerome Holland Int'l Living Center/ Marjorie Hart, 861015 (Box 18)
    - Trustee Council Registration - Roses in Barton, 861016 (Box 18)
    - Statler VIP's & tree with ribbon, 861017 (Box 18)
    - Henry Louis Gates, 861018 (Box 18)
    - Fellowship recipients / Robert McGinnis, 861019 (Box 18)
    - Panel Disc. W. Irv Chapman (trustee Council), 861020 (Box 18)
    - Aerials, 861021 (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes, 861022 (Box 18)
    - Slide Copies, 861023 (Box 18)
    - TV Rape Documentary / Sibley Dome / Uris Library, 861024 (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes (libe tower, dogs, Arts Quad), 861025 (Box 18)
  - November 1986
    - News Service, 861101 (Box 18)
    - Development, 861102 (Box 18)
    - Engineering Panel & Dean Streett, 861103 (Box 18)
    - Halloween Contest & World's Longest Chorus Line, 861104 (Box 18)
    - ILR / Performing Arts Construction, 861105 (Box 18)
    - Jason Seeley Car, 861106 (Box 18)
    - FR Newman Reception & Luncheon, 861107 (Box 18)
    - FR Newman Arboretum Dedication of 10-31 / Womens' Field Hockey, 861108 (Box 18)
    - Womens' Field Hockey / Football CU vs Bucknell, 861109 (Box 18)
    - Bucknell Football Game, 861110 (Box 18)
    - Sheila Tobias, 861111 (Box 18)
    - David Lewis / Maurice Gonnaud, 861112 (Box 18)
    - Profs. Strike & Baer, 861113 (Box 18)
    - Theatre Arts (Bruce Levitt & Maurice Daniels, 861114 (Box 18)
    - Benefair, 861115 (Box 18)
    - Statler Demolition, 861116 (Box 18)
    - Contemporary Music Festival Rehersal w Karel Husa, 861117 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Shanties at AD White House, 861118 (Box 18)
    - Federation Weekend / Statler Demolition / Homecoming / Nina Bassack & Brian Maynard / Benjamin Ginsberg, 861119
      - Contact sheet (Box 18)
    - Hans Bethe, 861120 (Box 18)
    - Collegetown Check to Plantations / PAC / Pigeons Vaccinations, 861121 (Box 18)
    - Undergrad Admissions for Minorities Seminar, 861122 (Box 18)
    - Drug Test Protest (Pee-in, 861123 (Box 18)
    - Cornell vs Penn Football, 861124 (Box 18)
    - Pacemaker Batteries-William Greatbatch, 861125 (Box 18)
    - Architecture Students, 861126 (Box 18)
    - Ken Wilson, 861127 (Box 18)
    - Dorothy Nelkin, 861128 (Box 18)
    - Alfred Kahn, 861129 (Box 18)
    - Chem - New Lab Kits, 861130 (Box 18)
    - Chemistry,[illegible], 861131 (Box 18)
    - Baker Inst. (color, 861132 (Box 18)
  - December 1986
    - News Service, 861201
      - Contact sheet (Box 18)
      - Contact sheet (Box 18)
    - Development, 861202 (Box 18)
    - Newman Professorship Dedication & Luncheon/Stone Hall Demo/ Pleasure and Repentance, 861203
      - Contact sheet (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes, 861204 (Box 18)
    - President Rhodes, 861205 (Box 18)
    - World's Longest Coffee Break, 861206 (Box 18)
    - Madrigal Feast (WSH, 861207 (Box 18)
    - Law School - Moot Court, 861208 (Box 18)
    - Cornell vs Harvard Hockey, 861209 (Box 18)
    - Engineering - Carpenter Computer Room, 861210 (Box 18)
    - Donna Jean Roberts (Rhodes Scholar, 861211 (Box 18)
    - Dr. Michels (NY City Med Col, 861212 (Box 18)
    - Studying (Uris & Fine Arts Library, 861213 (Box 18)
    - Gligor Taskovich (student, 861214 (Box 18)
    - Sage Windows, 861215 (Box 18)
    - Kevin Holcombe (student), 861216 (Box 18)
    - Eric Zimmerman & Paul Martecchini (students), 861217 (Box 18)
    - Barbara Baird, 861218 (Box 18)
    - Mark Lacey / Exams, 861219 (Box 18)
    - Yuri Orlov, 861220 (Box 18)
    - Judy Nguyen (student), 861221 (Box 18)
    - Fraternities & Sororities (color) (ID's included, 861222 (Box 18)
    - Hotel Staff Group Photo (color, 861223 (Box 18)
  - January 1970
    - News Service, 870101 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870102 (Box 19)
    - Yvonne Meinwald, 870103 (Box 19)
    - Yolena Baranova, 870104 (Box 19)
    - photo copy - Diane-Kari-te - kanawa, 870105 (Box 19)
    - Carol O' Brian Farewell, 870106 (Box 19)
    - Chem lab in Baker-Olin (film crew-Sagan, 870107 (Box 19)
    - Dennis Williams, 870108 (Box 19)
    - Prof. Lundberg (Blanchard Professorship, 870109 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes - new lens, 870110 (Box 19)
    - Baker Institute, 870111 (Box 19)
    - Gretchen Meyer, 870112 (Box 19)
    - Telluride, 870113 (Box 19)
    - President Rhodes, 870114 (Box 19)
    - Slide copy-computer graphic of solar map, 870115 (Box 19)
    - Campus Map (ink version, 870116 (Box 19)
    - Campus Map-CU owned buildings, 870117 (Box 19)
  - February 1987
    - News Service, 870201 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870202 (Box 19)
    - ILR, 870204 (Box 19)
    - U Hall dedication, 870205 (Box 19)
    - ILR/ new IBM Computer Dedication, 870206 (Box 19)
    - Black Gospel at Bailey Hall, 870207 (Box 19)
    - Campus Store - Valentine's Day promotion, 870208 (Box 19)
    - Campus scene - three coeds, 870209 (Box 19)
    - Gamelan / Campus Scenes / Fred Marcham, 870210 (Box 19)
    - Engineering, 870211 (Box 19)
    - Dayvvd Greenwood, 870212 (Box 19)
    - Women's Basketball, 870213 (Box 19)
    - Women's Gymnastics, 870214 (Box 19)
    - Slide copies - E. V. Baker & crew, 870215 (Box 19)
    - Men's Basketball - Dartmouth * Harvard, 870216 (Box 19)
    - Labs - chemistry, biology, archeology / Music - Sonya Monosoff, 870217 (Box 19)
    - Aaron Lewis - Lasar Beam, 870218 (Box 19)
  - March 1986
    - News Service, 870301 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870302 (Box 19)
    - Engineering students brochure, 870303 (Box 19)
    - Sandra Day O'Connor, 870304 (Box 19)
    - Female Faculty / Ag Day, 870305 (Box 19)
    - Gamelon, 870306 (Box 19)
    - Alumni House (color, 870307 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - Carpenter Computer Room, 870308 (Box 19)
    - Peter Saul - Ballet Class, 870309 (Box 19)
    - Green Dragon, 870310 (Box 19)
    - Dick Brown & Villa Banfi Awards, 870311 (Box 19)
    - Language Lab / Prof. Hsu & Student, 870312 (Box 19)
    - Lacrosse / Prof. Bianco-Math./ John Henderson-Anthropology, 870313 (Box 19)
    - John Henderson cont. / Language Labs, 870314 (Box 19)
    - Music - Susan Wyner & William Austin / Giuseppe Pizzotti - Hotel, 870315 (Box 19)
    - Prof. Kaufman - visiting Law prof., 870316 (Box 19)
    - Engineering / Campus Scenes / [illegible], 870317 (Box 19)
    - Ann McCann - Admissions check / John Hsu, 870318 (Box 19)
    - Copy work - Thailand book & photos, 870319 (Box 19)
    - Tim DeVoogd - Psych. Lab, 870320 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes, 870321 (Box 19)
    - Slide copy - Shoals Marine Lab, 870322 (Box 19)
  - April 1987
    - News Service, 870401 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870402 (Box 19)
    - Putu Wijaya, 870403 (Box 19)
    - Entrepreneur of the year, 870404 (Box 19)
    - ?, 870405 (Box 19)
    - Watch face, 870406 (Box 19)
    - ?, 870407 (Box 19)
    - Dame Kiri TeKanawa / engineering brunch-parents & Students, 870408 (Box 19)
    - Dr. Sy Rizi-Food Science Lab/Theory Center Model, 870409 (Box 19)
    - Landscape Architecture / "Loose Ends" - Theatre, 870410 (Box 19)
    - Plant Science / Landscape Architecture, 870411 (Box 19)
    - Livestock Show, 870412 (Box 19)
    - Jane Brown Writing Class / Microbiology Lab, 870413 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Co-op's 40th Anniversary, 870414 (Box 19)
    - Bicycle Time Trials, 870415 (Box 19)
    - Livestock Show / Malcolm Bilson-music / Baseball, 870416 (Box 19)
    - Ti Kwan Do, 870417 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes in Spring, 870418 (Box 19)
    - John Hsu-music / Baseball / Infant testing-Hum Ecol / Campus Scenes, 870419 (Box 19)
    - Info Center Volunteers / Campus Scenes / MVR, 870420 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Physice, 870421 (Box 19)
    - HEC, 870422 (Box 19)
    - Fred Marcham (slide copy, 870423 (Box 19)
  - May 1987
    - News Service, 870501 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870502 (Box 19)
    - American Adolescent Roundtable at MVR, 870503 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Convention and Awards Dinner/General Motors, 870504 (Box 19)
    - Glee Club at Sage Chapel, 870505 (Box 19)
    - Race Seminar at MVR/Hasbrouck Apartments, 870506 (Box 19)
    - Campus Map, 870507 (Box 19)
    - Phi Psi 500, 870508 (Box 19)
    - Guest Choreographer with students, 870509 (Box 19)
    - Willard Straight Dining/Campus Store, 870510 (Box 19)
    - Springfest, 870511 (Box 19)
    - Tom Sokol, 870512 (Box 19)
    - RPU_ The Purcells, 870513 (Box 19)
    - Equine Research Park/Springfest '87, 870514 (Box 19)
    - Campus Store, 870515 (Box 19)
    - Engineering-Bridge Building, 870516 (Box 19)
    - Art Event on Arts Quad, 870517 (Box 19)
    - Fred Marcham Scholarship, 870518 (Box 19)
    - Computer Fair, 870519 (Box 19)
    - Student Art-Architecture, 870520 (Box 19)
    - Hasbrouck Apartments/Purcells at RPU * Hasbrouck Apartments * Olin Library/Cornell Quarters, 870521
      - Contact sheet (Box 19)
    - Pres. Rhodes w/Prof. Erickson and students/WSH, 870522 (Box 19)
    - Library Annex, Entomology Libe, Olin Libe, 870523 (Box 19)
    - Africana Center/Exams, 870524 (Box 19)
    - Campus Store/Campus Scenes, 870525 (Box 19)
    - Senoir Party 5/25, 870526 (Box 19)
    - Campus Store, 870527 (Box 19)
    - Prof. Peter Katzenstein, 870528 (Box 19)
    - Baseball/Campus Store, 870529 (Box 19)
    - Check Passing/Hartell Gallery, 870530 (Box 19)
    - Arts and Sciences Reunion Project, 870531 (Box 19)
    - Graduation * Trustee Picnic * Mario Cuomo/Trustee Picnic * Cuomo Convocation * Graduation, 870532
      - Contact sheet (Box 19)
    - Hotel School Graduation Awards/Construction, 870533 (Box 19)
    - Presidential Scholars, 870534 (Box 19)
    - Senior Reception-Browsing Library, 870535 (Box 19)
  - June 1987
    - News Service, 870601 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870602 (Box 19)
    - VIP Farewell - Adams, Herbster, Spencer, Egner, 870603 (Box 19)
    - Copy negatives - woman on lawnmower, Cornell Calendar cover, 870604 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes, 870605 A&B (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 870606 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Car / Campus Scenes, 870607 (Box 19)
    - Asian Studies - Olin Library, 870608 (Box 19)
    - Van Tienhoven Award, 870609 (Box 19)
    - Students on Campus, 870610 (Box 19)
    - Service Awards Banquet, 870611 (Box 19)
    - Reunion Weekend, 870612 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - Formula car / sundial, 870613 (Box 19)
    - Binenkorb - Wall and portrait / Tobin Field House, 870614 (Box 19)
    - Captain Berger & Pres. Rhodes / Entrepot / Alumni House, 870615 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes, 870617 (Box 19)
  - July 1987
    - News Service, 870701 (Box 19)
    - Development, 870702 (Box 19)
    - Hinny, 870703 (Box 19)
    - Waterfalls and windsurfing, 870704 (Box 19)
    - Mary Lawrence luncheon, 870705 (Box 19)
    - Submicron, 870706 (Box 19)
    - Alumni Conference, 870707 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Interns at NCR, 870708 (Box 19)
    - Cass Park Marina, 870710 (Box 19)
    - Aaron Lewis - copy experimental work (color, 870711 (Box 19)
    - Chemistry faculty (color, 870712 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 870713 (Box 19)
    - Jazz Concert, 870714 (Box 19)
    - CAU, 870715 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School Certificates, 870716 (Box 19)
    - Pat Leary's Computer, 870717 (Box 19)
    - Summer Session, 870718 (Box 19)
    - A D White Library (illegible) (illegible, 870719 (Box 19)
  - August 1987
    - Untitled, 870801 (Box 19)
    - Telluride, 870802 (Box 19)
    - Hinny, 870803 (Box 19)
    - Chemistry Faculty, 870804 (Box 19)
    - Beebe Lake, 870805 (Box 19)
    - Chemistry - check passing, 870806 (Box 19)
    - Business Seminar - Summer Session, 870807 (Box 19)
    - Ithaca 5 & 10, 870808 (Box 19)
    - Beebe Lake, 870809 (Box 19)
    - Upson Hall addition & exterior, 870810 (Box 19)
    - Libe Tower, 870811 (Box 19)
    - Orientation, Moving in, etc., 870812 (Box 19)
    - Orientation, registration / Statler int. demolition, 870813 (Box 19)
    - SEAP slide copies, 870814 (Box 19)
    - AD White Library (6x7) "not used in display. See 870719", 870815 (Box 19)
    - SEAP slide copies, 870816 (Box 19)
    - Umbrellas C.S., 870817 (Box 19)
    - Orientation Faculty Tea / book store rush, 870818 (Box 19)
    - Fun in the Sun / C.S., 870819 (Box 19)
  - September 1987
    - Untitled, 870901 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 870902 (Box 19)
    - Snee Hall rock Garden, 870903 (Box 19)
    - WSH terrace / view from Clark Hall roof, 870904 (Box 19)
    - SAE Engr Car, 870905 (Box 19)
    - Equine Research Park, 870906 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 870907 (Box 19)
    - Engr Plaque and interiors, 870908 (Box 19)
    - Views from West Hill, 870909 (Box 19)
    - Three Arts & Sci faculty, 870910 (Box 19)
    - Slide Copies- Dr. Holly, Binenkorbs, 870911 (Box 19)
    - Engr Check passing/ Prof. Resnick, Prof. Ruppert, 870912 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum, 870913 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 870914 (Box 19)
    - Rosewood table, 870915 (Box 19)
    - UAW pickets, 870916 (Box 19)
    - Theory Center site with balloons, 870917 (Box 19)
    - Edmund Muskie, 870918 (Box 19)
    - Colgate Football, 870919 (Box 19)
    - Employee Day, 870920 (Box 19)
    - Law School dedication, 870921 (Box 19)
    - Tradition Fellowship Reception, 870922 (Box 19)
    - Students in ILR / C.S., 870923 (Box 19)
    - ILR - IBM visit, 870924 (Box 19)
    - Law School - visiting Prof. Ruden, 870925 (Box 19)
  - October 1987
    - Olin Library room dedication, 871002 (Box 19)
    - Theory Center proposed site, 871003 (Box 19)
    - Undergraduate school closeups/ Law School Plaque dedication on C 4 (also 871014, 871004
      - Contact sheet (Box 19)
    - Stained Glass Windows, 871005A (Box 19)
    - Slide Copies, 871005B (Box 19)
    - Homecoming, 871006 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Alum Breakfast, 871007 (Box 19)
    - Nanofab / Steve Sangren, 871008 (Box 19)
    - Theory Center model, 871009 (Box 19)
    - Cornell Tradition Symposium, 871010 (Box 19)
    - Performing Arts Center, 871011 (Box 19)
    - Plasma Physics Breakfast and Banquet, 871012 (Box 19)
    - Handicapped student, 871013 (Box 19)
    - Aerials / Law School plaque dedication (871004, 871014 (Box 19)
    - Trustee Scholarship Reception [illegible], 871015 (Box 19)
    - Bulb planting by Beebe Lake, 871016 (Box 19)
    - Aerials, 871017 (Box 19)
    - Simon Wiesenthal, 871018 (Box 19)
    - State of the University address, 871019 (Box 19)
    - SEAP, 871020 (Box 19)
    - Sir Oliver Wright, 871021 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum - Shuerer, 871022 (Box 19)
    - Engr - AT & T; awards, 871023 (Box 19)
    - Slide copies - architect models, 871024 (Box 19)
    - Hasbrouck Halloween Parade, 871025 (Box 19)
    - Libe slope scene, 871026 (Box 19)
  - November 1987
    - Untitled, 871101 (Box 19)
    - Anabel Taylor religious Services, 871102 (Box 19)
    - Students at work, 871103 (Box 19)
    - ILR / Engineering J.J & visiting Prof. / Engineering Robotic Mouse, 871104 (Box 19)
    - Bookstore Halloween, 871105 (Box 19)
    - Law School profs, 871106 (Box 19)
    - Law School Forum, 871107 (Box 19)
    - Phillip Morrison, 871108 (Box 19)
    - Building & Care Staff, 871109 (Box 19)
    - Pierre Salinger, 871110 (Box 19)
    - Baker Institute, 871111 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - Prof. Lovelace, 871112 (Box 19)
    - Art work for Enterprise, 871113 (Box 19)
    - Nutritional Science, 871114 (Box 19)
    - Stained Glass windows & mosaics, 871115 (Box 19)
  - December 1987
    - Prof. Borden - Music, 871201 (Box 19)
    - Prof. Silicano - Law, 871202 (Box 19)
    - Visiting Alum to ILR, 871203 (Box 19)
    - Super Conductor Seminar at Clark, 871204 (Box 19)
    - Law School Tower construction, 871205 (Box 19)
    - Sage Chapel interiors, 871206 (Box 19)
    - Construction / NANOFAB, 871207 (Box 19)
    - Engineering female student in Phillips Hall, 871208 (Box 19)
    - Santa Claus at Hasbrouck, 871209 (Box 19)
  - January 1988
    - Prof. Latham, 880101 (Box 19)
    - Construction/ BTI, 880102 (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 880103 (Box 19)
    - Thor Rhodin and grad. student, 880104 (Box 19)
    - Engr. Jim Mayer & Randy Phillips, 880105 (Box 19)
    - Prof. Charles Curran / Charlotte Heth, 880106 (Box 19)
    - Fencing, 880107 (Box 19)
    - Wilson Synchrotron, 880108 (Box 19)
    - Cornell Track Meet, 880109 (Box 19)
    - NNF tour for Digital Corp. and A.D. White Lunch, 880110 (Box 19)
    - Statler Roof Tree Topping, 880111 (Box 19)
    - Pressbox Int., 880112 (Box 19)
    - Jim Ranger-Moore - Olin fellow, 880113 (Box 19)
    - Manuscripts (color, 880114 (Box 19)
    - Joel Porte, 880115 (Box 19)
    - Margaret Wilder, 880116 (Box 19)
    - Clark Hall Int., 880117 (Box 19)
    - Augusta Simon - Faculty Fellow, 880118 (Box 19)
    - Super Computer, 880119 (Box 19)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 880120 (Box 19)
    - Language House, 880121 (Box 19)
    - Vernon Briggs - Dir. Hispanic Program, 880122 (Box 19)
    - Engr. Brochure, 880123 (Box 19)
    - PAC / Sheldon Court, 880124 (Box 19)
    - Baker Institute, 880125 (Box 19)
  - February 1988
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 880201 (Box 19)
    - Gymnastics, 880202 (Box 19)
    - Morrill-Language Lab, 880203 (Box 19)
    - Snow Scenes / Sally / Marty, 880204 (Box 19)
    - ENGR-Electron Microscope, 880205 (Box 19)
    - Bethany Center-Horseheads "Sr. Citizens with Dogs", 880206 (Box 19)
    - Joyce Lindoff-Guest Harpsichordist, 880207 (Box 19)
    - Black girl in Baker Laboratory (chemistry, 880208A (Box 19)
    - Dean's Reception Engr., 880208B (Box 19)
    - Engineering Cadif Facility, 880209 (Box 19)
    - Professor Shealy, 880210 (Box 19)
    - String Quarter-Barnes Auditorium, 880211 (Box 19)
    - Black Gospel-Bailey Hall, 880212 (Box 19)
    - Nanofab Laboratory, 880213 (Box 19)
    - Copy NEGS, 880214 (Box 19)
    - Mary Beth Norton, 880215 (Box 19)
    - Dance-Drummond Studio, 880216 (Box 19)
    - Polo, 880217 (Box 19)
    - Campus Map Displays, 880218 (Box 19)
  - March 1988
    - Views from west Hill - silhouette, 880301 (Box 19)
    - Africana Center, 880302 (Box 19)
    - Festival of Contemporary Music, 880303 (Box 19)
    - Disabled Weight Lifting, 880304 (Box 19)
    - Near Eastern Studies - David Patterson, 880305 (Box 19)
    - Copy negs - Baker Institute & NANOFAB, 880306 (Box 19)
    - Campus Scenes, 880307 (Box 19)
    - Near Eastern Studies - Debra Lipstat, 880308 (Box 19)
    - Purcell Union Interiors, 880309 (Box 19)
    - NANOFAB / Paul Tasker & Lester Eastman, 880310 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum - Frank Mickleman, 880311 (Box 19)
    - Afternoon Views from West Hill, 880312 (Box 19)
    - JGSM Reunion brochure, 880313 (Box 19)
    - Green Dragon, 880314 (Box 19)
    - slide copies - NANOFAB, 880315 (Box 19)
    - NANOFAB - Dinsmore, 880316 (Box 19)
    - Rockefeller interior renovations (color, 880317 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum-Roberta Romano, 880318 (Box 19)
    - Hennessy Scholarships and tasting - Hotel, 880319 (Box 19)
    - Bartell Lecture Series, 880320 (Box 19)
  - April 1988
    - RPU, 880401 (Box 19)
    - Scapin at Drummond, 880402 (Box 19)
    - Computer Screens in Architecture, 880404 (Box 19)
    - Book copies, 880405 (Box 19)
    - Western Society lecture, 880406 (Box 19)
    - Ken McClane, 880407 (Box 19)
    - Law School Centennial, 880408 (Box 19)
    - Walter Cohen, 880409 (Box 19)
    - Campus Map in display cases, 880410 (Box 19)
    - Cornell vs Penn Track Meet, 880411 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 880412 (Box 19)
    - H.E.C., 880413 (Box 19)
    - NANOFAB - 10th Anniversary, 880414 (Box 19)
    - Russell Osgood - new dean in Law School, 880415 (Box 19)
    - Near Eastern Studies - Adele Berlin, 880416 (Box 19)
    - Richard Epstein - Moot Court Room, 880417 (Box 19)
    - Law - Greg Alexander, Jon Macey, Clare Dalton, 880418 (Box 19)
    - C.S. - Oxley, Beebe Lake, etc., 880419 (Box 19)
  - May 1988
    - Computer Sciences, 880501 (Box 19)
    - WSH interiors, 880502 (Box 19)
    - U Hall #3, 880503 (Box 19)
    - Entrepreneur of the Year, 880504 (Box 19)
    - C. S. / Tree planting for Centennial, 880505 (Box 19)
    - RPU / Transfer students, 880506 (Box 19)
    - Baker Institute, 880507 (Box 19)
    - Blind Student Bonnie Zoladez, 880508 (Box 19)
    - Chilled Water plant, 880509 (Box 19)
    - JGSM students going to NY / and a doggie, 880510 (Box 19)
    - Presidential Scholars (color, 880511 (Box 19)
    - Commencement, 880512 (Box 19)
    - Hotel Library, 880513 (Box 19)
  - June 1988
    - C.S., 880601 (Box 19)
    - Violin, 880602 (Box 19)
    - Engineering professor Michael Todd, 880603 (Box 19)
    - Employee Awards, 880604 (Box 19)
    - Statler mock guest rooms, 880605 (Box 19)
    - Executive Staff, 880606 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 880607 (Box 19)
    - Carl Sagan, 880608 (Box 19)
    - Copy negs., 880609 (Box 19)
    - 3 Engineering Professors, 880610 (Box 19)
    - Copy negs., 880611 (Box 19)
    - Bill Thompson and Joyceln Hart / Copy negs., 880612 (Box 19)
    - Law School, 880613 (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 880614 (Box 19)
    - Dale Corson, 880615 (Box 19)
    - Russell Osgood new Law School Dean, 880616 (Box 19)
    - Harry Stewart - Engineering, 880617 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School CPD program, 880618 (Box 19)
  - July 1988
    - Executive Staff, 880701 (Box 19)
    - PAC, 880702 (Box 19)
    - RPU Exteriors, 880703 (Box 19)
    - Hotel CPD program, 880704 (Box 19)
    - Bill Huling, 880705 (Box 19)
    - Deena's, 880706 (Box 19)
    - Bonnie Zoladez, 880707 (Box 19)
    - Copy Work, 880708 (Box 19)
    - Sailboats in Marina, 880709 (Box 19)
  - August 1988
    - Hotel School Management Program, 880801 (Box 19)
    - CAU, 880802 (Box 19)
    - Students in Financial Aid Office, 880803 (Box 19)
    - Baker Institute, 880804 (Box 19)
    - Buttermilk Falls, 880805 (Box 19)
    - Sailing, 880806 (Box 19)
    - Newman Lab, 880807 (Box 19)
    - RPU's Hungry Bear, 880808 (Box 19)
    - Johnson Museum Interiors, 880809 (Box 19)
    - Statler Hotel Welcome Back Receptions, 880810 (Box 19)
    - PAC EXT. & Int., 880811 (Box 19)
  - September 1988
    - Engineering - lasers, 880901 (Box 19)
    - C. S., 880902 (Box 19)
    - Kitty Dukakis, 880903 (Box 19)
    - Computer Services at Lynah, 880904 (Box 19)
    - Mother Mallard, 880905 (Box 19)
    - Engineering in Clark Hall, 880906 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 880907 (Box 19)
    - Libe Tower, 880908 (Box 19)
    - Hydrolic Lab with Prof Jirka, 880909 (Box 19)
    - Inge Reichenbach, 880910 (Box 19)